You do not live in tabs
Telegram-first bid ops — no dashboard babysitting
Reviewed & enhanced with Claude Code
GeBIZ skill watches the market
Public listings, awarded prices, supplier signals
Claude scores fit + hidden compliance
Context memory, fit scoring, clarification questions
Genspark generates deck + quote
Submission-ready artifacts from one tender
Human approves before anything is sent
Yes, edit, or no — on your phone
Managed agents handle bid ops
Monitoring, matching, artifacts, outreach, handoffs
Creators focus on the work they love
Shoot, teach, produce, perform — let the bot bid
A portable bid-ops loop for creators, artists, and SMEs